Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Afrika Bambaataa recordings
      - Perfect beat, 2003; SR-21057; Kid Crème; Soul Sonic Force (Box 164)
        Catalog # NSB001; A-side Matrix # NSB 001 A
      - Rock the house EP (disc one), 1997; SR-21058; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21059. Double album. Annotated. Test pressing
      - Rock the house EP (disc two), 1997; SR-21059; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21058. Double album. Annotated. Test pressing
      - Warlocks and witches, computer chips, microchips and you (disc one), 1995; SR-21060; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21061. Double album. Annotated. Test pressing
        Catalog # PRO 1464; A-side Matrix # PRO-1464-1-A
      - Warlocks and witches, computer chips, microchips and you (disc two), 1995; SR-21061; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21060. Double album. Annotated. Test pressing
        Catalog # PRO 1464; A-side Matrix # PRO-1464-1-C
      - Push Pt. 2, 2004; SR-21062; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21063. Multiple copies. Annotated. Test pressing
      - Push Pt. 2, 2004; SR-21063; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21062. Multiple copies. Annotated. Test pressing
      - Everyday people - the breakbeat party album (disc one), 2004; SR-21064; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21065; SR-21066; SR-21067. Multiple copies; Double album. Annotated. Test pressing
        Catalog # PRM 00061; A-side Matrix # PRM-00061 A
      - Everyday people - the breakbeat party album (disc one), 2004; SR-21065; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21064; SR-21066; SR-21067. Multiple copies. Annotated. Test pressing
      - Everyday people - the breakbeat party album (disc one), 2004; SR-21066; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21064; SR-21065; SR-21067. Multiple copies. Annotated. Test pressing
      - Everyday people - the breakbeat party album (disc two), 2004; SR-21067; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21064; SR-21065; SR-21066. Double album.Test pressing
        Catalog # PRM 00061; A-side Matrix # PRM-00061 C
      - The wildstyle (disc one), 1983; SR-21068; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21069. Double album. Annotated. Test pressing
        Catalog # CEL 165; A-side Matrix # 12 IS 135 A-1U-1-1-1
      - The wildstyle (disc two), 1983; SR-21069; Time Zone; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21068. Double album. Annotated. Test pressing
        Catalog # CEL 165; A-side Matrix # 12 IS 135 B-1U-1-1-
      - If you technolectro; Funky & proud, 2002; SR-21070; Sirius B; Hardy Hard; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21071. Multiple copies. Annotated. Test pressing
        Catalog #; A-side Matrix # B147576-01 A1 HL
      - If you technolectro; Funky & proud, 2002; SR-21071; Sirius B; Hardy Hard; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21070. Multiple copies. Annotated. Test pressing
      - Funk (this is Jungle Sky 6) (disc one), 1999; SR-21072; Afrika Bambaataa; DJ Soul Slinger (Box 164)
      - Got to get up, 1997; SR-21073; Afrika Bambaataa; Carpe Diem (Box 164)
        Catalog # 12 MULTY 41 PX; A-side Matrix # 12 MULTY 41 PX-A-01-01-
      - No title, SR-21074; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog #; A-side Matrix #
      - No title, SR-21075; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
      - Clap, SR-21076; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog #; A-side Matrix # JP-0010-A
      - Sure shot electro, SR-21077; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog #; A-side Matrix # 2OT 002-A1
      - No title, 2004; SR-21078; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
      - Booty phat classics (disc one), 2001; SR-21079; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21080. Double album.
        Catalog # XR 275-1; A-side Matrix # LJ R 275-A
        Lil' Joe Records
      - Booty phat classics (disc two), 2001; SR-21080; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21079. Double album.
        Catalog # XR 275-1; A-side Matrix # LJ R 275-C
      - Genius of rap, 1982; SR-21081; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # ISSP 4007; A-side Matrix # ISSP 4007 A-2U
        Island Records
      - Spirit of the forest, 1989; SR-21082; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # 0-96551; A-side Matrix # ST-DN-57198-DMM-2
        Beverly Hills, California
      - Battle of the year 2001 - the soundtrack (disc one), 2001; SR-21083; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21084. Double album.
        Catalog # 586 700-1; A-side Matrix # B156863-01 A1 HL
        Def Jam Germany
      - Battle of the year 2001 - the soundtrack (disc two), 2001; SR-21084; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21083. Double album.
        Catalog # 586 700-1; A-side Matrix # B156863-02 C1 HL
      - Trilogy (disc one), 1996; SR-21085 (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21086; SR-21087. Triple album.
        Catalog # CELL 80808; A-side Matrix # CELL-6119 A
      - Trilogy (disc two), 1996; SR-21086; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21085; SR-21087. Triple album.
        Catalog # CELL 80808; A-side Matrix # CELL-6120 A
      - Trilogy (disc three), 1996; SR-21087; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21085; SR-21086. Triple album.
        Catalog # CELL 80808; A-side Matrix # CELL-6121 A
      - The ultimate mix, 1996; SR-21088; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # MM-PR 006; A-side Matrix # MM-PR-006 A1 MK
        Marlboro Music
      - Old school rarities - the funky drum jams, 1980; SR-21089; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # OSF LP 4011; A-side Matrix # OSF-4011-A OLD SCHOOL RARITIES THE FUNKY DRUM JAMS
        Ol' Skool Flava
      - Steppin' out records - the album 3 (disc one), 1995; SR-21090; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # STEP 003 LP; A-side Matrix # STEP LP003 A-1
        Steppin' Out Records
        Midlothian, United Kingdom
      - Steppin' out records - the album 3 (disc two), 1995; SR-21091; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # STEP 003 LP; A-side Matrix # STEP LP003 C-1
      - Beat Street (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) - Volume 1, 1984; SR-21092; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21093. Different discs.
        Catalog # 80154-1; A-side Matrix # ST A 845469-A
        Atlantic
      - Beat Street (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) - Volume 1, 1984; SR-21093; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21092. Different discs.
        Catalog # 780 154-1; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf 780154-1 A
      - Disconet Program Service Volume 7 Program 10 (Disc 1), 1985; SR-21094; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # MWDN710A; A-side Matrix # MWDN-710 A
        Disconet Program Service
      - Renegades of funk, 1984; SR-30928; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 94)
        Annotated. Mold remediated
        Catalog # TB 839; A-side Matrix # TB-839-A